searchofficespace.com 2017-06-06

# Search Office Space | Privacy Policy

**User Information Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which SOS Worldwide Limited (“SOS”) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User” or “you”) of the [www.searchofficespace.com](http://www.searchofficespace.com/) and affiliated websites (“Sites”). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by SOS.

For the purpose of the [Data Protection Act 1998](http://www.legislation.gov.uk/ukpga/1998/29/contents) (the “Act”), the data controller is SOS, with registered address at 1st Floor, 7-10 Chandos Street, London, W1G 9DQ, UK.

** ** **Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, phone number. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilised and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use “cookies” to enhance User experience. User’s web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**How we use collected information**

SOS will only use the details provided by you as part of your registration:

  * to send periodic emails;
  * for the purposes of your registration and the administration of the SOS website;
  * for the business purposes of SOS;
  * to contact you (including sending information and updates relating to any order, questions or requests) or for the provision of customer services; and
  * to supply such details to any operators or landlords of suitable office accommodation or business centres that are registered with SOS to enable them to make contact with you at their discretion.

If the User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users’ personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes unless you have asked us not to do so at registration or afterwards.

We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group from time to time, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and its subsidiaries, as defined in section [1159 of the UK Companies Act 2006.](http://www.legislation.gov.uk/ukpga/2006/46/section/1159)

We may disclose your personal information to third parties:

  * In the circumstances set out above.
  * In the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets.
  * If SOS or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, in which case personal data held by it about its customers will be one of the transferred assets.
  * If we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use or terms and conditions and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of SOS, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

SOS has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Email Marketing**

If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe link at the bottom of each email.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:

Search Office Space

**Contacting us**

Head Offices

**• Stanmore Business & Innovation Centre, Howard Road, Stanmore, Middlesex, HA7 1GB, United Kingdom**

 **• 1500 Broadway, 5th Floor, Suite 505, New York, NY 10036, United States**

e-mail address: info@searchofficespace.com or submit the form on the [contact page](http://www.searchofficespace.com/row/dyna/office-space/contact.html).

_This document was last updated in April 2017_
